http://www.teenidols4you.com/privacy.html

: TOP 50 IDOLS
NEW PICTURES : IDOL BIRTHDAYS : SITE UPDATES : UPLOAD A PICTURE : ALL IDOLS : CONTACT US : SEARCH
Privacy Notice
Last updated: May 10, 2018
Thank you for visiting www.teenidols4you.com . Teen Idols 4 You is committed to honoring and protecting your privacy while at the same time providing you with a first rate on-line experience. As an important part of respecting your privacy, we believe that you have the right to know what information is collected by this Web site, how such information may be used, and what security measures are taken to protect your information.
Collection and Use of Information
When you visit our Web site, and/or contact us via e-mail, certain information is or may be collected. Among the types of information that may be collected are the following:
Domain names of visitors to our site;
"navigational information" regarding the traffic patterns of our Web site, including the number of visits to a particular page and user-specific information on which pages a guest visits, average length of time spent on the site and similar site usage data; and
Any information that you may choose to submit in connection with any e-mail messages, on-site surveys, registry programs, photo uploads, contests and the like. This infomation may also include network data as in your IP and domain infomation.
We use this information in order to analyze, manage and improve our Web site so that we may continually strive to provide you with the best experience that we possibly can. Information on traffic patterns and the number of page visits and the like helps us to further develop and improve our site layout to better meet your needs. Of course, we also use information such as your name, e-mail address to contact you, respond to your inquiries, or we may use such information to notify you of services, special offers, new products and other services that we believe may be of interest to you, or to notify you of important new changes in our Web site. Finally, we use collected information to help us diagnose problems with our server or other technical issues relating to the performance of the Web site.
Information Collected by Our Advertising Partners
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
Please reference Google's Privacy Policy .
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.
Value Click Media, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
Please reference Value Click Media's Privacy Policy .
Tribal Fusion/Exponential Interactive, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data
in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online
advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or
complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.
Users who would like more information can view Exponential Interactive privacy policy here.
Our partners Google, Google DoubleClick, TribalFusion, and Value Click Media are compliant members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI).
The NAI is a voluntary compliance initiative to help protect your privacy.
If you would like to opt-out of targeted advertising by
by any NAI compliant member simply visit http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
At this site you can also track your opt-out status by NAI member as well as determine if you have received a cookie
from any of the members.
Cookies
"Cookies" are small bits of data that a web site can send to your browser and may then be stored on your hard drive. We use cookies in connection with certain features on our Web site, although we note that our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information such as your name. We use the cookies to enable us to help provide you with customized or tailored information or services. You can set your web browser so that you will always be notified when you receive a cookie.
Security
Teen Idols 4 You makes every effort to protect the security of your personal information. Any personal information that you provide is encrypted so that no-one can read it while it is being transmitted over the Internet. Any information collected by us is stored in private files behind a firewall designed to protect your information by denying unauthorized access by outside users.
Providing Information to Outside Parties
Teen Idols 4 You will never sell, trade, rent or otherwise provide your personal information to any outside parties.
Teen Idols 4 You may provide aggregate statistics about our guests, sales, traffic patterns and other site usage information to certain third parties, but none of this material would include any personally identifying information. Teen Idols 4 You may also release any information when we believe in good faith that we are required to do so under applicable law or that such a release is necessary or advisable in order to protect the rights, property or safety of Teen Idols 4 You , our guests and users, or others, or to enforce the terms and conditions applicable to this Web site.
Third Party Sites
Our Web site may contain links to other sites maintained by third parties unrelated to Teen Idols 4 You. While we of course attempt to link only to reputable sites, please be aware that we do not monitor and is in no way responsible for the content or privacy practices of any such third party sites.
Our Policy Towards Children
Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at chad_w@galacticstudio.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.
Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Galatic Studio's (teenidols4you.com) rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party's, including a government's, request to disclose your information.
The Galactic Studio
TeenIdols4you.com
P.O. Box 8187
Jacksonville, AR 72078-8187
+1.501 436-9570
Username:
Password:
Sign Up Free!
Forgot Your Password?
Follow Us
Twitter
VIEW MOBILE SITE
Most Popular Idols
Asher AngelJacob TremblayEduardo ValentaAustin AbramsCameron Dallas
Explore The Site
Actor Photos
Singer Photos
New Photos
Upload Photos
Top 50 Idols
| TeenIdols4you Terms & Conditions | Copyright Policy | Privacy Policy | Hosted By DigitalOcean |
Copyright © 2020 The Galactic Studio. All rights reserved.Photos & certain artwork used on TeenIdols4You are copyright protected and are the property of their respective owners.
Studio logos & other trademarks used herein are the property of their respective owners.
